{
    "questions":[
        {"question":"Why is it a dumb idea to use the same password on multiple sites?", 
            "incorrect":"Because I lose access to multiple accounts if I forget my password.", 
            "correct":"Because if a hacker obtains the password, he or she can get into my more sensitive accounts, such as my e-mail or bank account."},

        {"question":"Why is your e-mail account one of the most sensitive accounts you got?",
            "incorrect":"Because it is one of the most frequently used accounts of mine.", 
            "correct":"Because if a hacker gets access to my e-mail account, he or she can use the reset function on other sites to get access to those too."},

        {"question":"Is it a good idea to write your password on a piece of paper to remember it?", 
            "incorrect":"Absolutely not!", 
         "correct":"If it helps me use unique passwords and I keep it save."},

        {"question":"Should I keep my password on a post-it note on my screen?", 
           "incorrect":"Yes.", 
         "correct":"No."},

        {"question":"Why should I use symbols in my password?", 
           "incorrect":"Because they are pretty.", 
         "correct":"Because it raises the number of passwords for a hacker to try from 2 billion to 513,798 billion"},

        {"question":"Why should I change password a few times per year?", 
           "incorrect":"Because it helps me forget my older passwords.", 
         "correct":"Because a company might have been hacked and lost your password."},

        {"question":"Are password managers bad?", 
           "incorrect":"Yes.", 
         "correct":"No."},

         {"question":"Could I use a poem to remember my password?", 
           "incorrect":"Yes. I should use the first few words of something from a famous Shakespeare play!", 
         "correct":"Yes. I should use a personal poem and use the first and second letter of a few words, and add some numbers and symbols!"},

         {"question":"Should I use my email address as a password?", 
           "incorrect":"Yes. Since it is unique, no one will guess it.", 
         "correct":"No."},

	{"question":"Why should I use a password manager?", 
           "incorrect":"Because it helps me fill in passwords.", 
         "correct":"Because it helps me remember my unique, complex passwords."},

        {"question":"Should I use web sites to test my passwords strength?", 
           "incorrect":"Yes. Those web sites are great to find out if my password is strong or not!", 
         "correct":"No, since it might save my password."}
    ]    
}
